greenvelope.com 2019-12-18

# Terms and Privacy | Greenvelope.com

## Terms for Hosts

#### I. BINDING AGREEMENT

A. These Terms of Service (this "Agreement") constitute a binding and enforceable agreement between the Event Host and Greenvelope. Please read this Agreement carefully.

B. For purposes of this Agreement, each person or entity hosting, producing, selling tickets for an event or service for which tickets are sold or to which invitations are issued (each an "Event"), and each of their authorized agents or service providers, shall be an "Event Host." Each person purchasing a ticket to an event through Greenvelope for the Event shall be a "Purchaser." Each person to receive an invitation to an Event shall be a "Guest." 

C. Greenvelope, LLC ("Greenvelope") provides web-based ticketing and invitation and attendance management services to Event Hosts for Events. Greenvelope is not affiliated with any Event Host and solely acts an intermediary between the Event Host and the Purchaser or Guest. 

D. This Agreement applies only to the specific Event which Event Host has engaged Greenvelope for ticketing or invitation and attendance management services, and any other events hosted or produced by Event Host shall be governed by a separate agreement. 

#### II. EVENTS

A. _Advertising_. This Agreement does not create any obligation on the part of Greenvelope to sponsor, support, advertise, promote, or otherwise perform any action on behalf of the Event Host with respect to, or in furtherance of, any Event. 

B. _Use of Information_. If Event Host chooses to enable a public event page for any Event, Greenvelope may, in its sole and absolute discretion, use information provided by Event Host regarding such Event in publically accessible information on the Greenvelope website and other marketing, promotion, and business development purposes.

C. _Limitation of Liability_. Greenvelope shall have no liability with regard to any Event for which it provides ticketing or invitation and attendance management services, except as specifically set forth in this Agreement. Greenvelope’s total liability under this Agreement shall not exceed the sum of all amounts actually received by it from Purchasers and Event Hosts.

#### III. REPRESENTATIONS AND WARRANTIES OF EVENT HOST

A. _Representations & Warranties_. Event Hosts agrees, and represents and warrants to Greenvelope that: 

  1. Event Host is authorized to sell tickets or provide invitations to the Event.
  2. The number of tickets Event Host determines to sell, or invitations the Event Host reasonably believes will be accepted, for the Event is within the all applicable regulations and restrictions concerning the venue, including state, local and federal law and regulation, and any restrictions imposed by the Event venue. 
  3. Event Host is responsible for all state, local, federal and other taxes with respect to the Event and the sale of tickets therefore. 
  4. Event Host owns or is otherwise entitled to use, all material posted to the Greenvelope website by Event Host or provided to Greenvelope for any purpose, and the use of such material or information does not infringe on any patent, copyright, or other intellectual property right of any third party.

#### IV. TICKET PRICING; FEES

A. _Ticket Prices_. Event host shall be solely responsible for setting the ticket price or prices for the Event. 

B. _Service Fees_. Event Host shall pay to Greenvelope the service fees set forth on the Pricing Schedule available at <https://www.greenvelope.com/business-invitations#pricing>. In the case of Events for which Event Host retains Greenvelope to provide invitation and attendance management services, Event Host shall pay the service fees in advance. 

#### V. CAPACITY; INVITATIONS; REFUNDS

A. _Capacity_. Event Host shall determine, for each Event, the number of tickets available for purchase or invitations to be extended. Event Host is solely responsible for this determination and Greenvelope shall have no liability for oversold tickets or excess invitations, or to any attendee at an Event, to any venue, or to any other party with regard to tickets sold or invitations extended beyond the legal capacity of any venue.

B. _Refunds_.

  1. _**ALL SALES ARE FINAL**_. In the event that any ticket purchased by a Purchaser is unusable by such Purchaser because of the over-sale of tickets or the cancellation of the Event, or if the Event is rescheduled or moved to a new venue, Event Host agrees to be fully and solely responsible to Purchaser for any refunds or ticket exchanges, and Greenvelope shall have no liability or obligation in connection therewith. Greenvelope will not be obligated to issue refunds to any Event Host purchasing invitation and attendance management services for any reason.

#### VI. UNLIMITED MEMBERSHIP USE

A. Event hosts purchasing an annual unlimited membership are able to create unlimited mailings/events as long as each mailing is unique in nature. Cloning and creating a mailing/event in order to get around purchasing a larger package will flag your account for review. Continuing to behave in this manner will be deemed abusive and cause suspension of your account without refund. 

#### VII. SMS TEXTING LIMITS

A. Every paid Greenvelope account includes a maximum of 1000 text messages. This limit can be increased at a price of $20 USD per 1000 for typical use cases. If you are sending to a large number of non-US numbers, there may be an additional cost. Please contact us at support@greenvelope.com for assistance upgrading your text message limits.

#### VIII. OPT IN MAILING LISTS; SPAM/ABUSE COMPLAINTS

A. _Mailing Lists_. Event hosts sending mailings/events that are sales/marketing in nature, may only send to email addresses that have specifically opted in to receive sales/marketing communications from event host. It is not permissiable to send to a contact list that has been purchased, rented, or aquired in any manner not consistent with the recipient having opted in to receive communications. Failure to adhere to this guideline can result suspension of your account without refund.

B. _Spam Complaints_. Greenvelope does not tolerate unsolicited/spam messages being sent from our system. In the event that cards/messages sent from your account generate a high amount of spam complaints reported to Greenvelope by email providers (AOL, Yahoo, Hotmail, etc.), Greenvelope reserves the right to suspend your account without refund.

#### IX. ACCOUNT SETTLEMENT

A. _Records_. If Greenvelope is retained by Event Host to sell tickets for the Event, during the ticket sales period for the Event, and through the date on which the Event Host's Greenvelope account is active and in good standing, Greenvelope shall maintain complete and accurate records of all ticket sales made on behalf of the Event Host for the Event, including the ticket price paid and the service fee paid for each ticket. 

B. _Remittance_. If Greenvelope is retained by Event Host to sell tickets for the Event, payments will be processed via Stripe. Once you are set-up with Stripe, transfers arrive in your bank account on a 2-day rolling basis. Or you can opt to receive transfers weekly or monthly. Please check Stripe.com for details on the latest transfer protocols.

#### X. INDEMNIFICATION

A. _Indemnification_. Event Host agrees to forever indemnify and hold harmless Greenvelope, its members, managers, officers, employees and agents, and its contractors or customers, from and against all claims, suits, damages, losses, liabilities, or expenses of any kind, including reasonable attorneys’ fees, arising from, or in connection with, or which may have been caused, or are alleged to have been caused, directly or indirectly, by any act of omission or commission, negligent or otherwise, of Event Host or by Event Host’s failure to comply with the terms of this Agreement, any requirement of law, rule or regulation, including any rule, regulation or policy promulgated by any venue, and including without limitation, the representations and warranties relating contained herein. The parties agree that this indemnification obligation shall survive until any claim, action or cause of action respecting the above is fully and finally barred by the applicable statute of limitation. 

#### XI. MISCELLANEOUS

A. _Waiver_. Any failure on the part of any Party to comply with any of its obligations, agreements or conditions hereunder may be waived by any other Party to whom such compliance is owed. No waiver of any provision of this Agreement shall be deemed, or shall constitute, a waiver of any other provision, whether or not similar, nor shall any waiver constitute a continuing waiver.

B. _Assignment_. Neither this Agreement nor any rights hereunder shall be assignable by either party hereto without the written consent of the other party. Any such assignment in violation of this provision shall be void and of no force or effect.

C. _Binding Effect_. This Agreement shall be binding upon and inure to the benefit of each of the parties and their respective heirs, legal representatives, executors, administrators, successors and permitted assigns.

D. _Cumulative Remedies_. The rights and remedies of the parties set forth herein are cumulative and not alternative, and each party shall have all other rights and remedies not inconsistent with this Agreement as provided by law or in equity.

E. _Headings_. The section and other headings in this Agreement are inserted solely as a matter of convenience and for reference, and are not a part of this Agreement.

F. _Entire Agreement_. This Agreement, and the other documents linked herein, including the Pricing Schedule and the Privacy Policy, contain and constitute the entire agreement among the parties and supersede and cancel any prior agreements, representations, warranties, or communications, whether oral or written, among the parties relating to the transactions contemplated by this Agreement. 

G. _Severability_. The provisions of this Agreement are severable and the invalidity of one or more of the provisions herein shall not have any effect upon the validity or enforceability of any other provision.

H. _Consent to Conduct Business Electronically_. The parties may use and rely upon electronic records and electronic signatures for execution and delivery of this Agreement and any other agreement, understandings, notices, disclosures or other documents, communications or information of any type sent or received in accordance with this Agreement.

I. _Disclaimer of Warranties_. Event Host understands and hereby acknowledges that Greenvelope provides all services on an "as is" and "where is" basis, and Greenvelope makes no warranty or representation regarding, and assumes no responsibility for, the timeliness, accurate transmission, or retention of any communication effect through its website or otherwise. Greenvelope disclaims all liability for, and makes no representation or warranty regarding, the availability of its website from any region or for any user. Greenvelope shall not be obligated to perform any service required to be performed by it under this Agreement in the event that such performance is made impossible or impractical by any internet outage, delay, unauthorized access, act of God, or other contingency outside of Greenvelope’s control.

J. _Amendment_. This Agreement may not be amended, supplemented or otherwise modified except by a written agreement executed by both parties.

K. _DISPUTES_. EXCEPT AS OTHERWISE EXPRESSLY PROVIDED IN THIS AGREEMENT, ANY CONTROVERSY OR CLAIM ARISING OUT OF OR RELATING TO THIS AGREEMENT OR ANY OTHER AGREEMENT CONTEMPLATED HEREUNDER, OR THE INTERPRETATION OR BREACH HEREOF OR THEREOF, SHALL BE SUBMITTED TO BINDING ARBITRATION CONDUCTED IN KING COUNTY, WASHINGTON, IN ACCORDANCE WITH THE THEN CURRENT COMMERCIAL ARBITRATION RULES OF THE AMERICAN ARBITRATION ASSOCIATION, UNLESS OTHERWISE AGREED. IF THE PARTIES ARE UNABLE TO AGREE ON THE SELECTION OF AN ARBITRATOR TO RESOLVE THE DISPUTE WITHIN FIFTEEN (15) DAYS OF EITHER PARTY GIVING THE OTHER PARTY NOTICE OF ITS INTENT TO INVOKE THIS SECTION, THEN EITHER PARTY MAY MAKE A REQUEST OF THE AMERICAN ARBITRATION ASSOCIATION FOR A LIST OF QUALIFIED POTENTIAL ARBITRATORS FROM WHICH THE PARTIES SHALL SELECT AN ARBITRATOR IN ACCORDANCE WITH THE COMMERCIAL ARBITRATION RULES OF THE AMERICAN ARBITRATION ASSOCIATION. IF NO ARBITRATOR IS THUS SELECTED WITHIN FIFTEEN (15) DAYS AFTER SUCH LIST IS SUBMITTED TO THE PARTIES, EITHER PARTY MAY REQUEST THE AMERICAN ARBITRATION ASSOCIATION TO SELECT SUCH ARBITRATOR. SUBJECT TO THE FOLLOWING SENTENCE, ALL EXPENSES AND FEES OF THE ARBITRATOR AND ANY OTHER EXPENSES OF THE ARBITRATION WILL BE BORNE EQUALLY BY PARTIES UNLESS THE ARBITRATOR IN THE AWARD ASSESSES SUCH EXPENSES AGAINST ONE OF THE PARTIES OR ALLOCATES SUCH EXPENSES OTHER THAN EQUALLY BETWEEN THE PARTIES. EACH PARTY WILL BEAR ITS OWN ATTORNEYS’ FEES AND EXPENSES, UNLESS THE ARBITRATOR FINDS THAT THE CLAIM OR DEFENSE OF ANY PARTY WAS FRIVOLOUS OR LACKED A REASONABLE BASIS IN FACT OR LAW, IN WHICH CASE THE ARBITRATOR MAY ASSESS AGAINST SUCH PARTY ALL OR ANY PART OF THE ATTORNEYS’ FEES AND EXPENSES OF THE OTHER PARTY. THE DETERMINATION OF SUCH ARBITRATOR SHALL BE FINAL AND BINDING UPON THE PARTIES AND JUDGMENT MAY BE ENTERED THEREUPON IN ANY COURT HAVING JURISDICTION THEREOF.

In the event that the immediately preceding paragraph is deemed to be unenforceable, the parties hereby agree as follows: Any litigation between the parties will be commenced and maintained only in the courts of King County, Washington, or in the United States District Court for the Western District of Washington in Seattle, Washington, and each of the parties consents to the jurisdiction of such courts (and of the appropriate appellate courts) in any such action or proceeding and waives any objection to venue laid therein, provided, however, that Greenvelope may seek to obtain injunctive relief in any court that Greenvelope may select. Process in any action or proceeding referred to in the preceding sentence may be served on any party anywhere in the world.

## Terms for Ticket Purchasers

#### I. BINDING AGREEMENT

A. These Terms of Service (this "Agreement") constitute a binding and enforceable agreement between Purchaser and Greenvelope (each a "party," and together the "parties," hereto). Please read this Agreement carefully. 

B. For purposes of this Agreement, each person or entity hosting, producing, selling tickets for an event or service for which tickets are sold (each an "Event"), and each of their authorized agents or service providers, shall be an "Event Host." Each person purchasing a ticket to an event through Greenvelope for the Event shall be a "Purchaser." 

C. Greenvelope, LLC ("Greenvelope") provides web-based ticketing services to Event Hosts for Events. Greenvelope is not affiliated with any Event Host and solely acts an intermediary between the Event Host and the purchaser of tickets for each Event. Purchaser assumes all of the risk associated with attendance at the Event.

#### II. EVENTS AND EVENT INFORMATION

A. The price and availability of Tickets for the Event are set by the Event Host. In addition to the ticket price, an Event Host may require that Purchaser pay the service fees charged by Greenvelope. The Pricing Schedule setting out the service fees is available at <https://www.greenvelope.com/business-invitations#pricing>. The service fees, if any, which Purchaser will be charged will be also be set out on the Event page on the Greenvelope website.

B. The Event Host determines the number of tickets available for purchase for the Event. Event Host is solely responsible for this determination and Greenvelope shall have no liability for oversold tickets. 

C. All information concerning the Event, including venue seating charts is provided by the Event Host and is not independently confirmed by Greenvelope. Event Host is solely responsible for this information and Greenvelope shall have no liability for any misrepresentation or inaccuracy in such information.

#### III. TICKETING

A. _Delivery_. All Event tickets will be delivered via e-mail to the address provided by Purchaser when purchasing such ticket. Greenvelope is not responsible for, and Purchaser expressly assumes, all risk related to delivery or non-delivery, loss, theft, delay, damage or destruction during delivery. Upon completion of the purchase of tickets by a Purchaser, Greenvelope will supply an e-mail receipt to Purchaser setting forth the details of the tickets purchased. In some instances, Greenvelope or the Event Host may offer replacement tickets for lost, stolen or undelivered tickets to Purchasers holding receipts. 

B. _Refunds_. 

  1. **_ALL SALES ARE FINAL_**. In the event that any ticket is unusable by Purchaser because of the over-sale of tickets or the cancellation of the Event, or if the Event is rescheduled or moved to a new venue, Purchaser agrees to look solely to Event Host for any refunds or ticket exchange. 

C. _Transaction Cancellation_. Greenvelope reserves the right to cancel any order placed on the Greenvelope website at any time prior to the processing of Purchaser’s payment for any reason or no reason.

D. _Resale_. Tickets purchased through Greenvelope are for use only by Purchaser and may not be resold. Any resold ticket will be automatically voided and no refund will be issued. 

#### IV. PRIVACY POLICY; USE OF PURCHASER INFORMATION

A. Purchaser’s use of the Greenvelope website, including to purchase tickets to the Event, is governed by this Agreement and Greenvelope’s Privacy Policy . In the event of any conflict or inconsistency between any of the terms and provisions hereof and the Privacy Policy, this Agreement shall control.

B. Greenvelope gives the Event Producer the option to require purchasers to allow certain personal information to be disclosed to the Event Host. In these cases, the information to be disclosed will be described at the time of purchase, and by completing the purchase of tickets Purchaser irrevocably grants Greenvelope the right and authority to disclose such information. Purchaser may also elect to provide certain information to the Event Host, even where it is not required. In no event will Greenvelope be responsible for the Event Host’s use or further disclosure of any information provided by Greenvelope.

#### V. MISCELLANEOUS

A. _Waiver_. Any failure on the part of any party to comply with any of its obligations, agreements or conditions hereunder may be waived by any other party to whom such compliance is owed. No waiver of any provision of this Agreement shall be deemed, or shall constitute, a waiver of any other provision, whether or not similar, nor shall any waiver constitute a continuing waiver.

B. _Assignment_. Neither this Agreement nor any rights hereunder shall be assignable by either party hereto without the written consent of the other party. Any such assignment in violation of this provision shall be void and of no force or effect.

C. _Binding Effect_. This Agreement shall be binding upon and inure to the benefit of each of the parties and their respective heirs, legal representatives, executors, administrators, successors and permitted assigns.

D. _Cumulative Remedies_. The rights and remedies of the parties set forth herein are cumulative and not alternative, and each party shall have all other rights and remedies not inconsistent with this Agreement as provided by law or in equity.

E. _Headings_. The section and other headings in this Agreement are inserted solely as a matter of convenience and for reference, and are not a part of this Agreement.

F. _Entire Agreement_. This Agreement, and the other documents linked herein, including the Pricing Schedule and the Privacy Policy, contain and constitute the entire agreement among the parties and supersede and cancel any prior agreements, representations, warranties, or communications, whether oral or written, among the parties relating to the transactions contemplated by this Agreement. 

G. _Severability_. The provisions of this Agreement are severable and the invalidity of one or more of the provisions herein shall not have any effect upon the validity or enforceability of any other provision.

H. _Consent to Conduct Business Electronically_. The parties may use and rely upon electronic records and electronic signatures for execution and delivery of this Agreement and any other agreement, understandings, notices, disclosures or other documents, communications or information of any type sent or received in accordance with this Agreement.

I. _Disclaimer of Warranties_. Purchaser understands and hereby acknowledges that Greenvelope provides all services on an "as is" and "where is" basis, and Greenvelope makes no warranty or representation regarding, and assumes no responsibility for, the timeliness, accurate transmission, or retention of any communication effect through its website or otherwise. Greenvelope disclaims all liability for, and makes no representation or warranty regarding, the availability of its website from any region or for any user. Greenvelope shall not be obligated to perform any service required to be performed by it under this Agreement in the event that such performance is made impossible or impractical by any internet outage, delay, unauthorized access, act of God, or other contingency outside of Greenvelope’s control.

J. _Amendment_. This Agreement may not be amended, supplemented or otherwise modified except by a written agreement acknowledged by both parties.

K. _DISPUTES_. EXCEPT AS OTHERWISE EXPRESSLY PROVIDED IN THIS AGREEMENT, ANY CONTROVERSY OR CLAIM ARISING OUT OF OR RELATING TO THIS AGREEMENT OR ANY OTHER AGREEMENT CONTEMPLATED HEREUNDER, OR THE INTERPRETATION OR BREACH HEREOF OR THEREOF, SHALL BE SUBMITTED TO BINDING ARBITRATION CONDUCTED IN KING COUNTY, WASHINGTON, IN ACCORDANCE WITH THE THEN CURRENT COMMERCIAL ARBITRATION RULES OF THE AMERICAN ARBITRATION ASSOCIATION (INCLUDING THE THEN CURRENT CONSUMER RELATED DISPUTE SUPPLEMENTARY PROCEDURES, IF APPLICABLE), UNLESS OTHERWISE AGREED. IF THE PARTIES ARE UNABLE TO AGREE ON THE SELECTION OF AN ARBITRATOR TO RESOLVE THE DISPUTE WITHIN FIFTEEN (15) DAYS OF EITHER PARTY GIVING THE OTHER PARTY NOTICE OF ITS INTENT TO INVOKE THIS SECTION, THEN EITHER PARTY MAY MAKE A REQUEST OF THE AMERICAN ARBITRATION ASSOCIATION FOR A LIST OF QUALIFIED POTENTIAL ARBITRATORS FROM WHICH THE PARTIES SHALL SELECT AN ARBITRATOR IN ACCORDANCE WITH THE COMMERCIAL ARBITRATION RULES OF THE AMERICAN ARBITRATION ASSOCIATION (INCLUDING THE THEN CURRENT CONSUMER RELATED DISPUTE SUPPLEMENTARY PROCEDURES, IF APPLICABLE). IF NO ARBITRATOR IS THUS SELECTED WITHIN FIFTEEN (15) DAYS AFTER SUCH LIST IS SUBMITTED TO THE PARTIES, EITHER PARTY MAY REQUEST THE AMERICAN ARBITRATION ASSOCIATION TO SELECT SUCH ARBITRATOR. SUBJECT TO THE FOLLOWING SENTENCE, ALL EXPENSES AND FEES OF THE ARBITRATOR AND ANY OTHER EXPENSES OF THE ARBITRATION WILL BE BORNE EQUALLY BY PARTIES UNLESS THE ARBITRATOR IN THE AWARD ASSESSES SUCH EXPENSES AGAINST ONE OF THE PARTIES OR ALLOCATES SUCH EXPENSES OTHER THAN EQUALLY BETWEEN THE PARTIES. EACH PARTY WILL BEAR ITS OWN ATTORNEYS’ FEES AND EXPENSES, UNLESS THE ARBITRATOR FINDS THAT THE CLAIM OR DEFENSE OF ANY PARTY WAS FRIVOLOUS OR LACKED A REASONABLE BASIS IN FACT OR LAW, IN WHICH CASE THE ARBITRATOR MAY ASSESS AGAINST SUCH PARTY ALL OR ANY PART OF THE ATTORNEYS’ FEES AND EXPENSES OF THE OTHER PARTY. THE DETERMINATION OF SUCH ARBITRATOR SHALL BE FINAL AND BINDING UPON THE PARTIES AND JUDGMENT MAY BE ENTERED THEREUPON IN ANY COURT HAVING JURISDICTION THEREOF.

In the event that the immediately preceding paragraph is deemed to be unenforceable, the parties hereby agree as follows: Any litigation between the parties will be commenced and maintained only in the courts of King County, Washington, or in the United States District Court for the Western District of Washington in Seattle, Washington, and each of the parties consents to the jurisdiction of such courts (and of the appropriate appellate courts) in any such action or proceeding and waives any objection to venue laid therein, provided, however, that Greenvelope may seek to obtain injunctive relief in any court that Greenvelope may select. Process in any action or proceeding referred to in the preceding sentence may be served on any party anywhere in the world.

### Last updated May 25th, 2018

## Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy sets out how Greenvelope, LLC ("Greenvelope") collects, uses, and protects information gathered through the use of our website https://www.greenvelope.com/. Greenvelope values the privacy and security of your personal information1, and is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected and that we process your data in a fair and transparent manner. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

Greenvelope may change this Privacy Policy from time to time by updating this page. Whenever we make changes, we will prominently display a notice on the main page of our website, will provide a description of the changes to the policy, and will change the effective date listed above.

You should also check this page from time to time to ensure that you are happy with any changes that have been made. By accessing this website, you acknowledge your acceptance of the terms of this Privacy Policy and any changes to it. If we make significant changes to the way we process, share, or transmit your personal data, we will provide you with a more specific notice of such changes and will do so prior to implementing those changes.

### What Information We Collect

While you utilize the Greenvelope website, Greenvelope collects and stores the following information about you and your computer (the "Basic Information") :

  * The type and version of your Operating System and Web Browser;
  * Your computer’s IP address;
  * The date and time of your visit;
  * What page you visited; and
  * What page you came from.

In addition to the Basic Information, if you create an account with Greenvelope, we will also collect and store the following information (the "Account Information"):

  * Your name;
  * Your e-mail address;
  * Information you provide regarding your preferences and interests; and
  * Other information you specifically provide.

In addition to the Basic Information and the Account Information, if you utilize Greenvelope’s services, we also collect and store the following information (the "User Information"):

  * Payment information;
  * Contact information, including your address, phone number, and e-mail address;
  * If you are utilizing Greenvelope’s invitation services, information regarding your guests and invitees (the "Invitee Information"); and
  * Other information you specifically provide.

### How We Collect Information

**_Information Provided by Your Computer and Web Browser._**

Most web browsers automatically provide portions of the Basic Information to websites, but you can usually modify the settings to decline to provide portions of the information. This may prevent Greenvelope from working properly and prevent you from taking full advantage of the website.

**_Cookies._**

A cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your computer’s hard drive. Once you agree, the file is added and the cookie helps analyze web traffic or lets you know when you visit a particular site. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. The web application can tailor its operations to your needs, likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your preferences.

We use traffic log cookies to identify which pages are being used. This helps us analyze data about web page traffic and improve our website in order to tailor it to customer needs. We only use this information for statistical analysis purposes and the data is removed from the system.

Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us.

You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website.

**_Information You Provide._**

Most of the information we gather from you, including all of the Account Information and the User Information, we will gather from you directly using forms you complete on our website.

**_Information Provided by Our Customers._**

Customers who utilize our invitation services may also provide us information about you if you are a guest or invitee to the event for which the invitation service is utilized.

### What We Do With The Information We Collect

We use the information you provide for a variety of purposes, all of which are described in this Privacy Policy, including to better understand your needs and provide you with a better service. You have choices about the personal information1 we collect and how it will be used. As detailed below, we may use your personal information we collect when we have your consent. In particular, we use the Basic Information and the User Information for the following purposes:

  * Internal record keeping;
  * To improve our products and services;
  * To send promotional emails to you about new products, special offers or other information which we think you may find interesting using the email address which you have provided;
  * To contact you for market research purposes (we may contact you by email, phone, fax or mail;) and
  * To customize the website according to your interests.

If you do not want Greenvelope to continue sending you communications such as newsletters or announcements, you may opt out of receiving such communications by following the opt-out instructions that will be included in footer of the emails that we send you.

We also use the User Information to provide you with the service you have purchased or requested, including:

  * To process your order; 
  * To deliver invitations to your guests or invitees; 
  * To deliver tickets to you; 
  * To communicate with you.

In addition to the uses above, with your consent, Greenvelope may share the Basic Information, Account Information, and User Information with its parent, subsidiary and other related companies, trusted affiliates, independent contractors and business partners who will use the information for the purposes outlined above, but only as necessary to provide the services offered by Greenvelope, to provide the website itself, and for the specific purposes for which the information was collected. 

**_Legal compliance._**

Greenvelope may also share the Basic Information, Account Information, and User Information in response to a valid and enforceable request from law enforcement or other governmental agency or in response to subpoenas, court orders or other legal process. We may also share the Basic Information, Account Information, and User Information to establish, protect or exercise Greenvelope’s legal or other rights or to defend against a legal claim or as otherwise required or allowed by law. Greenvelope may disclose personal information in order to protect the rights, property or safety of a user of the Greenvelope website or any other person. Greenvelope may share the Basic Information, Account Information, and User Information to investigate or prevent a violation by you of any contractual or other relationship with Greenvelope or the perpetration of any illegal or harmful activity. 

**_Third party sharing._**

We will not sell, distribute, lease or otherwise share any Basic Information, Account Information, or User Information, including any e-mail addresses or other information, to third parties unless we have your permission or are required by law to do so. We may use your personal information to tell you about third parties which we think you may find interesting, though you may opt-out of receiving such communications.We may combine the Basic Information, Account Information, and User Information we collect for any of the foregoing uses.

We will never use any of the Invitee Information except in connection with the provision of services which you or your invitee or guest request. Your guests and invitees will not receive promotional or advertising e-mails from us, and we will not sell, distribute or lease any of the Invitee Information for this purpose. 

### How Do We Protect Your Information

We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorized access or disclosure we have put in place appropriate physical, technical and organizational procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.

In order to secure your personal information, access to your data is password-protected, and personal information is protected by SSL encryption, to the extent supported by your web browser, when it is exchanged between your web browser and the Greenvelope website. Because no security measures are perfect or impenetrable, Greenvelope cannot guarantee that the information submitted to, maintained on or transmitted from its systems will be completely secure.

### Links to Other Websites

Our website may contain links to enable you to visit other websites of interest easily. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide while visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this Privacy Policy. You should exercise caution and carefully review the privacy policies of such sites before inputting any personal information.

### How You Can Control Your Personal Information

You may choose to restrict the collection or use of your personal information in the following ways: 

If you have previously agreed to us using your personal information for direct marketing purposes, you may change your mind at any time by writing to or emailing us at [info@greenvelope.com](mailto:info@greenvelope.com).

If you wish to unsubscribe from receiving marketing emails from Greenvelope, LLC, please click the unsubscribe link included in the footer of all of our emails.

If you believe that any information we are holding on you is incorrect or incomplete, please email at [info@greenvelope.com](mailto:info@greenvelope.com). We will promptly correct any information found to be incorrect. You may also request that we delete the information we have collected about you at any time by emailing us at [info@greenvelope.com](mailto:info@greenvelope.com). Please note that in certain circumstances, we may not be able to completely remove your information from our systems. For example, we may retain your information for legitimate business purposes, if it may be necessary to prevent fraud or future abuse, for account recovery purposes, if required by law or as retained in our data backup systems or cached or archived pages, or where the burden or expense of accommodating your request would, in our good faith judgment, be disproportionate to the risks to your privacy, or where the rights of others may be violated. All retained personal information will continue to be subject to the terms of the Privacy Policy to which the User has previously agreed. Personal data will be retained only for as long as necessary for Greenvelope to be able to response to inquiries about prior account activity and audits related to prior purchases.

Finally, you may request access to the personal information we have collected about you by sending a request to [info@greenvelope.com](mailto:info@greenvelope.com). 

**EU-U.S. Privacy Shield and Swiss-U.S. Privacy Shield**

Greenvelope participates in and has certified its compliance with the EU-U.S. Privacy Shield Framework and the Swiss-US Privacy Shield Framework. Greenvelope is committed to subjecting all personal information received from European Union (EU) member countries, and Switzerland, respectively, in reliance on the Privacy Shield Framework, to the Framework’s applicable Principles. To learn more about the Privacy Shield Framework, visit the U.S. Department of Commerce’s Privacy Shield List at <https://www.privacyshield.gov/list>.

Greenvelope is responsible for the processing of personal information it receives, under each Privacy Shield Framework, and subsequently transfers to a third party acting as an agent on its behalf. Greenvelope complies with the Privacy Shield Principles for all onward transfers of personal information from the EU and Switzerland, including the onward transfer liability provisions.

With respect to personal information received or transferred pursuant to the Privacy Shield Framework, Greenvelope is subject to the regulatory enforcement powers of the U.S. Federal Trade Commission. In certain situations, Greenvelope may be required to disclose personal information in response to lawful requests by public authorities, including to meet national security or law enforcement requirements.

**General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR)**

Because we take the privacy and security of your information very seriously, including the information of our customers located in the EU, we are committed to protecting your personal information in accordance with the provisions of the GDPR.We have built privacy and security of personal information into our technical and organizational systems and processes related to any personal information we process.We do not sell, exchange or transfer personal information for any reason, without your consent, or for purposes other than those specifically described in this Privacy Policy.The personal information we collect is limited to that which is necessary to provide the products and services you request, and your information is only kept as long as necessary to fulfill the purposes for which it was collected.

* * *

1 As used in this Privacy Policy, the term "personal information" means "Basic Information," "Account Information," "User Information" and "Invitee Information" to the extent that such information constitutes "personal data" as defined by the General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR), or "personal information" or "personally identifiable information" as defined by various United States data breach notification statutes, or information that may otherwise be used to identify an individual.
